Guide to the Gregory E. Montes urban history and travel collection, 1798-1960.
Montes, Gregory E. urban history and travel collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gregory E. Montes urban history and travel collection, 1798-1960.
8035
Gregory E. Montes
6.2 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Travel brochures, city guides, maps, books of views, postcards, and related materials.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Travel brochures, city guides, maps, books of views, postcards, and related materials documenting world cities and tourism in the 19th and 20th centuries. The Montes collection also includes more than 1,000 books (most cataloged separately and searchable in the library catalog) on world cities and urban areas, the majority published between 1798 and 1960.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Montes, Gregory E.
Subjects:
Cities and towns--History.; Urbanization--History.; Travel.
Form and Genre Terms:
Brochures.; Travel guidebooks.; Maps.; Postcards.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Donated by Gregory E. Montes in memory of Dr. Gustavo E. and Marica S. Montes.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Books
United States
Non-United States
General, Africa, Asia, Australia/Oceania, Europe, North America
Series II. Guides
United States
Non-United States
General, Africa, Asia, Europe, North America, South America
Series III. Postcards
United States
Non-United States
General, Africa, Asia, Australia/Oceania, Europe, North America, South America
Series IV. Additional Items, Miscellaneous, Ephemera Posters, Artwork
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Books
  Only some books are listed here. The majority are available in the library catalog by searching for keywords Gregory Montes.
  - Books - United States
    - State / Region: Arizona, Southern Title: Gadsden's Silent Observers Author: Keasey, Merritt S. III (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Arizona, Yuma (Prison) Title: Prison Centennial 1876-1976 Author: Trafzer, Cliff / George, Steve (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Arizona, Yuma (Prison) Title: The Hell Hole Author: Brent, Wm. & Milarde (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Alameda Title: The Urban Area of the Alameda 1500-1520 Author: Gregory Montes, 8035 Bd. Ms. 1
      This is thesis prepared by Montes with the assistance of Professor George Kubler and his advisor Professor Heinrich Klotz in Spring of 1969.
    - State / Region: California, General Title: Indian Trail Author: Howe, Frank (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, General Title: Agustin V. Zamorano, Architect Author: Neuerburg, Norman (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Gulf Title: Tidepool Wonders of the Sea of Cortez III Author: Farmer, Wesley M. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles Title: Take an Alternate Route Author: Pierce, Paul (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles Title: Los Angeles Author: Handen, Richard (Box 14)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles Title: A Picture Tour of Los Angeles Author: Sunset Press (Box 14)
    - State / Region: California, Monterey Title: Ghosts, Bandits, and Legends Author: Reinstedt, Randall A. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Morro Bay Title: Morro Bay's Yesterdays Author: Bailey, Jane H. and Gates, Dorothy L. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, National City Title: The History of South West Lodge Author: F & A.M, Nat'l City, CA (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, National City Title: Exploring Joshua Tree Author: Mitchell, Roger (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Palo Alto Title: Discovering Portus Novae Albionis Author: Aker, Raymond / Von Der Porten, Edward (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Palo Alto Title: The Palo Alto Tree Author: Weymouth, Alice Jenkins (Box 15)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: The Boy Who Loved Music Author: Bac Vacher, Eugene (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: Women in San Diego... a history in photographs Author: Carlson, Dick (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: The Giant Dipper Author: Young, Geoffrey (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: Beginnings: San Diego Public Library History Author: Breed, Clare (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: Index to History of San Diego Author: Smythe, Wm. E. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: We Can Save San Diego Author: Gastil, Gordon (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Title: Don Diego's Old School Days Author: Dixon, Ben F. (Box 13)
    - Country / Region: California, San Diego Title: Convair Aerospace Division of General Dynamics Fiftieth Anniversary, 1923-1973 Author: General Dynamics (Box 13)
    - Country / Region: California, San Diego Title: Birding San Diego County, some Select Locales Author: San Diego Audubon Scoiety (Box 13)
    - Country / Region: California, San Diego Title: Mingei International's Seventeenth Anniversary Celebration, The New Museuom of Art of All People, Program, 1995 (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, Bay Title: Sounds of the Bay Author: Held, Ruth (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego Area Title: A Bibliography for San Diego County and Adjacent Regions of Southern California and Northern Baja California Author: Bouscaren, Stephen J. (Box 25)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: La Jolla, Year by Year Author: Randolph, Howard S.F. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: Salt Marsh Vegetation: Examples from the Tijuana Estuary Author: Zedler, Dr. Joy B. (Box 25)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: Inside La Jolla Author: La Jolla Historical Society (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: LA Jolla's House of Many Legends Author: Leftwich, James A. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: La Jolla Author: Andujar, Gloria (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: Reminscences Author: Bailey, Joshua Jr. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, La Jolla Title: Western Sketches and War Poems Author: Brackenbury, Richard (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, Los Penasquitos Lagoon Title: Environmental Evaluation and Planning Project Author: Gardner, Gwen (SDSU) (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego, Los Penasquitos Lagoon Title: Geology of Los Penasquitos Canyon Author: Northrop, John (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: Two Days in San Francisco Author: Klauber, Laurence (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: Our Family Album Author: Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Co. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: The Evanescent City Author: Sterling, George / Bruguiere, Francis (Box 15)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: Seeing San Francisco Author: Kollmann, M. (Box 15)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: Views of San Francisco and California Author: Nelson, L.H. (Box 15)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: Views of San Francisco Author: Burbank, E.A. (Box 15)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Title: Natural Color Studies of the Pan-Pac Internat'l Exposition Author: Reid, Robert A. (Box 15)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Bay Title: The Peraltas Author: Fibel, Pearl Randolph (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Jose Title: First Lady of Racho San Pablo, Martina Castro de Alvarado Author: Conley, Frances (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Santa Fe Title: Rancho Santa Fe: California's Perfectly Planned Community Author: Shippey, Lee (Box 25)
    - State / Region: California, Santa Fe Title: Rancho Santa Fe: California, Yesterday-Today Author: Sinnard, L.G. (Box 25)
    - State / Region: California, Scripps College Title: A Sampling from Travel Letters Author: Scripps, Ellen B. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Scripps College Title: Ellen Browning Scripps: Her Life and Times Author: Hepner, Frances K. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Scripps College Title: Walter Ray Hepner, Sr. Educator (In Memoriam) Author: Hepner, Frances K. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, SoCal Title: Founding Fathers of Southern California Author: LA Business Journal (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Temecula Title: The Historic Valley of Temecula Author: Parker, Horace (Box 13)
    - State / Region: California, Yosemite Title: Yosemite's Historic Wawona Author: Sargent, Shirley (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Colorado, Pike's Peak Title: Anemones: A Story from Pike's Peak Author: Dunbar, Susan T. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Florida, General Title: The Florida Buyers Digest Author: Gulf Guaranty Building (Box 13)
    - State / Region: General Title: America is Going Places Author: General Electric (Box 13)
    - State / Region: General Title: America's Best Beaches Author: Leatherman, Stephen P. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Hawaii, General Title: Here's Hawaii Author: Gray Line Hawaii (Box 13)
    - Country / Region: Hawaii, General Title: The Unbeatable Dream, The Story of the Napili Kai Beach Club Author: Millar, Jack, Margaret, and Dorothy (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Hawaii, Parker Ranch Title: The Story of Parker Ranch Author: Ornduff, Donald R. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago Title: Official Book of Views Author: Albert, Allen (Box 14)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago Title: Official View Book Author: Albert, Allen (Box 14)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston Title: Other Merchants and Sea Captains of Old Boston Author: Walton Advertising and Printing Co. (Box 15)
    - State / Region: New Mexico, Santa Fe Title: Rancho Santa Fe, Yesterday and Today Author: Nelson, Ruth R. (Box 13)
    - State / Region: New Mexico, Santa Fe Title: Echoes of Rancho Santa Fe Author: Clotfelter, Connie (Box 13)
    - State / Region: New York, New York Title: Presentation Ceremonies [statue of Simon Bolivar to US] Author: Bolivarian Society of the US (Box 14)
    - State / Region: New York, New York Title: New York, The Wonder City Author: American Art Publishing Co. (Box 14)
    - State / Region: New York, New York Title: New York (photos) Author: None given (Box 14)
    - State / Region: New York, New York Title: King's New York Views Author: Harris, N.W. (Box 14)
    - Country / Region: New York, New York Title: Honeymoon Miralda Project, Holly Solomon Gallery, Opening Program, 1991 (Box 14)
    - State / Region: New York, New York Title: Adventuring in New York Author: Frederick, J. George (Box 15)
    - State / Region: New York, New York Title: New York, The Wonder City Author: American Art Publishing Co. (Box 15)
    - State / Region: Nevada, Las Vegas Title: Out From Las Vegas Author: Lawlor, Florine (Box 13)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Philadelphia Title: Golden Slippers Author: Miers, Earl Schneck (Box 15)
    - State / Region: Texas, Fort Davis Title: Fort Davis: The Men of Troop H Author: Thybony, Scott (Box 25)
    - State / Region: Texas, San Angelo Title: San Angelo: Queen City of the Conchos (Box 25)
    - Country / Region: Washington, D.C. Title: Churches of the Presidents in Washington Author: Jones, Olga (Box 14)
    - Country / Region: Washington, D.C. Title: The Symbol and The Sword Author: District of Columbia Civil War Centennial Commission (Box 14)
  - Books - Non-United States
    - World, General
      - Country / Region: General Title: Architecture: city sense Author: Crosby, Theo (Box 19)
      - Country / Region: General, Norway Title: Architects Selected Works Author: Jarmund, Kristin (Box 19)
    - Africa
      - Country / Region: General Title: The Living Volutes of Africa Author: Aiken, D.W. / Fuller, K.J. (Box 19)
      - Country / Region: South Africa, Cape Town Title: Cape Town: South Africa's Mother City Author: Central News Agency (Box 19)
    - Asia
      - Country / Region: China, Bejing Title: Of Palaces and Pantheons Author: Beijing Review (Box 19)
      - Country / Region: China, Great Wall Title: Under Western Eyes Author: Dimock, George (Box 19)
      - Country / Region: Middle East, Pakistan Title: British Lithographs of Pakistan 1840-50 Author: Aijazuddin, F.S. and Shahnaz (Box 16)
    - Australia / Oceania
      - Country / Region: Australia, Northern Title: Up North: Australia Above Capricorn Author: Barrett, Charles (Box 19)
    - Australia / Oceania
      - Country / Region: New Zealand, Auckland Title: Albin Martin: Auckland City Art Gallery 1988 Author: Blackley, Roger and Una Platts (Box 25)
    - Europe
      - Country / Region: France, Paris Title: Paris: 32 Views Author: Hall, John B. (Box 25)
      - Country / Region: France, Paris Title: Paris Excursions (Box 25)
      - Country / Region: Germany, Munich Title: Munich: A Guide for Resident Foreigners Author: Gerber, Carl (Box 25)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Milan (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Venice (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: Scotland, Edinburgh Title: Edinburgh and Vicinity Author: Ritchie (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: Scotland, Edinburgh Title: Jamieson's Illustrated Guide to Edinburgh Castle Author: Jamieson, Hugh (Box 25)
      - Country / Region: Turkey, Constantinople, Istanbul Title: Istanbul Author: Cig, Kemal (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, Epping Forest Title: Souvenir of Epping Forest Author: Deeker, A.E. (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London Title: John O'London's Weekly Coronation Author: O'London, John (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London Title: London, Heat of the Empire Author: Valentine (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London Title: Old London Street Cries Author: Tuer, Andrew W. (Box 25)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London Title: London Flashbacks: A Book of 30 Black-and-White Historical Photographs (Box 25)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, Westminster Abbey Title: Westminster Abbey 900 Years Author: Nicholson, Robert (Box 16)
    - North America
      - Country / Region: Mexico Title: The Most Beautiful and Typical City in America Author: Sierra, A.P. (Box 16)
      - Country / Region: Panama Title: Pan-American Exposition (Box 19)
      - Country / Region: Haiti Title: Images of Haiti Author: Yonker, Dolores M. (Box 25)
- Series II. Guides
  - Guides - United States
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
    - State / Region: California, Palo Alto (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Includes Carlsbad
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco (Box 12, Folder 8-15)
    - State / Region: California, Misc. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
    - State / Region: Florida, Miami Beach (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - State / Region: Hawaii, Misc. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - State / Region: Louisiana, New Orleans 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - State / Region: Louisiana, New Orleans 2 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - State / Region: Missouri, St Louis (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 1 (Box 13, Folder 1, 2)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 4 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 5 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Philadelphia (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Philadelphia 2, Poconos, Pittsburgh (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: Pacific Northwest, Washington, Oregon (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - State / Region: Southwest, New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: US General, Misc. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Guides - Non-United States
    - World, General
      - Country / Region: World/US, Misc (Box 11, Folder 27)
        Includes Portugual, West Africa, Delhi India, Thailand
    - Asia
      - Country / Region: Egypt, Iran, Syria, Lebanon, Cairo, Philde, Iran, Damascus(2),Lebanon(1), Israel (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Country / Region: Japan, Misc (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Europe
      - Country / Region: General, General (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Country / Region: Austria, Vienna (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Country / Region: Eastern and Central Europe, Prague, Dubrovnik, Russia, Budapest, Croatia (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Country / Region: France, Avignon, Versailles, Paris (Box 11, Folder 9-12)
      - Country / Region: Germany, Poland, Cologne, Dresden, Frankfurt, Leipzig, Misc. (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Country / Region: Ireland, Dublin (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Rome (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Seville, Granada, Madrid (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Country / Region: Turkey, Misc. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London (Box 11, Folder 12-15)
    - North America
      - Country / Region: British Columbia, Canada (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Mexico City, Misc. (Box 11, Folder 21-23)
    - South America
      - Country / Region: Brazil, Rio de Janiero (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Series III. Postcards
  - Postcards - United States
    - State / Region: US General, Miscellaneous 1 # of packets: 7 # of items: 29 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: US General, Miscellaneous 2 # of packets: 2 # of items: 12 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: US General, Miscellaneous 3 # of packets: 3 # of items: 20 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      Includes: Boulder Dam, "In the Clouds" official folder, Saint Sophia Greek Orthodox Cathedral
    - State / Region: Alabama, Mobile, Bellingrath Gardens, Misc # of packets: 3 # of items: 29 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: Arizona, Mesa, Tucson, Scottsdale, Flagstaff,Phoenix # of packets: 7 # of items: 41 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - State / Region: Arizona, Grand Canyon, Jerome # of packets: 8 # of items: 28 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - State / Region: Arizona, Misc, Tonto Nat'l Monument # of packets: 2 # of items: 71 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - State / Region: California, Catalina Island # of packets: 8 # of items: 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: California, Hollywood # of packets: 12 # of items: 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles, Pasadena, Pomona # of packets: 8 # of items: 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles # of packets: 12 # of items: 20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 1 # of packets: # of items: 78 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 2 # of packets: # of items: 71 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 3 # of packets: # of items: 70 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 4 # of packets: # of items: 48 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 5 # of packets: # of items: 70 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 6 # of packets: # of items: 66 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 7 # of packets: # of items: 76 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: California, Los Angeles / Southern California Urban Region 8 # of packets: # of items: 66 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: California, Missions: S. Fernando, Ines, Capistrano, Miguel, Antonio, Gabriel, Misc # of packets: 4 # of items: 38 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: California, Long Beach, Santa Monica, Santa Barbara # of packets: 7 # of items: 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: California, Northern 1 # of packets: # of items: 46 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - State / Region: California, Northern 2 # of packets: 1 # of items: 42 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - State / Region: California, Solvang, San Simeon, Portuguese Bend # of packets: 2 # of items: 46 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: California, Monterey, Indio, Palm Springs, Rose Hills # of packets: 5 # of items: 55 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego 1 # of packets: 6 # of items: 32 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: California, San Diego 2 # of packets: 7 # of items: 21 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco 1 # of packets: 11 # of items: 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco 2 # of packets: 8 # of items: 23 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco 3 # of packets: 8 # of items: 8 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco 4 # of packets: 6 # of items: 18 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco (Mini Postcards) # of packets: 1 # of items: 21 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: California, San Francisco Bay Area / Sacramento / Northern California Urban Region 1 # of packets: # of items: 85 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - State / Region:California, San Francisco Bay Area / Sacramento / Northern California Urban Region 2 # of packets: # of items: 81 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - State / Region:California, San Francisco Bay Area / Sacramento / Northern California Urban Region 3 # of packets: # of items: 49 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - State / Region:California, San Francisco Bay Area / Sacramento / Northern California Urban Region 4 # of packets: # of items: 53 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: California, Carmel, Paso Robles, Big Sur, Santa Cruz, Berkeley, S.L.Obispo, Pacific Grove, La Canada, San Jose, Misc. # of packets: 2 # of items: 65 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: California, Yosemite # of packets: 3 # of items: 15 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: California, Death Valley, Deserts # of packets: 8 # of items: 49 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: California, General # of packets: 3 # of items: 13 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: California, Misc. Plants, Lakes, Mountains, Cities # of packets: 5 # of items: 71 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: California, Misc. # of packets: 0 # of items: 14 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: Colorado, Colorado Springs, Denver, Misc # of packets: 7 # of items: 30 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: Connecticut, Connecticut # of packets: 0 # of items: 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: Delaware, Delaware # of packets: 0 # of items: 6 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 1 # of packets: 9 # of items: 17 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 2 # of packets: 10 # of items: 10 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 3 # of packets: 8 # of items: 22 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 4 # of packets: 6 # of items: 31 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 5 # of packets: 5 # of items: 24 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 6 # of packets: 1 # of items: 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 7 - Capitol Building, National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception # of packets: # of items: 92 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 8 - South West Washington, D.C., National Mall # of packets: # of items: 80 (Box 22, Folder 2)